alright go ahead and get started first
好吧，先开始
of all think thank you for attending
所有人都认为谢谢您的参加
right there's a lot of options everyone
对，每个人都有很多选择
has here Java one during this time slot
在此时间段内有一个Java
and you're here with us so awesome so my
而且你在我们这里真是太棒了
name is John Klingon and I'll be
我叫约翰·克林贡，我会
moderating kind of this panel discussion
主持这种小组讨论
asking just a few kind of warm-up
问一些热身
questions to make sure everyone's on a
问题，以确保每个人都在
baseline a bit and then we'll be opening
基线，然后我们将打开
up the questions for everyone out in the
在每个人面前提出问题
audience
听众
Hey so first of all again I mentioned
嘿，所以我首先提到
giant clean I'm with Red Hat and kind of
超级干净，我和Red Hat在一起
been with the micro profile effort from
从
day one then we have David Blevins raise
第一天，我们有大卫·布列文
your hand as we go along with Tommy
当我们与汤米一起时，你的手
tribe and David Dell Abbasi Oracle and
部落和大卫·戴尔·阿巴西·甲骨文和
Kevin Sutter IBM alright and Mark little
凯文·萨特IBM不错，马克·李特
red hat and Mike Croft payara all right
红色帽子和Mike Croft payara没事
so these are the panelists and let's go
这些是小组成员，我们开始吧
ahead and get started with a few kind of
前进并开始几种
again seed questions and this is just
再次播出问题，这仅仅是
raise your hand if you want to answer
如果你想回答，请举手
this particular question yeah what is
这个特殊的问题是什么
micro profile not in like depth or
微观轮廓不像深度或
anything but why was the project created
除了什么，为什么创建这个项目
kind of in the first place and actually
放在首位，实际上
maybe even I'll take a step back raise
甚至连我都会退一步
your hand if you've heard of micro
你的手，如果你听说过微
profile excellent good excellent yes
简介优优优是
awesome
很棒
anyone want to kind of just do a quick
任何人都想做的只是快速
debrief in terms of you know the
关于您的汇报，您知道
foundation of the project and why we
项目的基础以及为什么我们
started the project and and so on sir I
开始了项目，等等，先生
guess I got volunteered okay that is one
我猜我是自愿的，好吧
one thing I John and I were were project
我和约翰在一起的一件事是项目
leads for the Eclipse project that
导致Eclipse项目的
doesn't mean that we have any more power
并不意味着我们有更多的力量
than anybody else but we you know we try
比其他任何人，但我们知道我们尽力了
to organize some of the activity so
组织一些活动，这样
Michael profile has been around what
迈克尔的个人资料一直围绕着
about 16 18 months started with just an
大约16到18个月才开始
idea with some of the industry leaders
与一些行业领导者的想法
on this panel and others in the audience
在此面板上以及其他观众中
trying to figure out okay how are we
试图弄清楚我们怎么样
going to fill in this gap with Java EE
将用Java EE填补这一空白
and creating micro services in the cloud
在云中创建微服务
I
一世
we you know Mike Java II was not moving
我们知道Mike Java II没动
fast enough it wasn't filling in those
足够快，没有填补那些
gaps what can we do and that's where the
差距我们该怎么办，那就是
idea of micro profile came up we first
微观轮廓的想法首先出现
presented it
提出了
what 2016 and now you know 2017 at this
什么2016年，现在你知道2017年
point we we've had our third release and
我们已经发布了第三版
I don't know if that's another one of
我不知道那是另一种吗
your seed questions I won't go into a
你的种子问题，我不会去
lot of detail there but we are
那里有很多细节，但是我们
generating some momentum it's been a
产生一些动力
very good conference today ordered this
今天非常好的会议命令了这个
week and we're you know looking forward
一周，我们知道您的期待
to the interaction with the group here
与这里的小组互动
anybody else want to add anything to the
任何人都想添加任何东西
history sorry I forgot to put on my
历史对不起，我忘了穿上我的
microphone profile hoodie just so Evan
麦克风轮廓连帽衫就这样Evan
can consent it maybe the marketing
可以同意，也许是营销
people told me I had to do this okay
人们告诉我，我必须这样做
just kidding
开玩笑
all right so let's say we had an
好吧，所以说我们有一个
announcement this JavaOne so does
宣布此JavaOne也是如此
somebody maybe want to talk about what
也许有人想谈什么
did we introduce this JavaOne in terms
我们用术语介绍了这个JavaOne吗
of micah profile i have one particular
的弥迦档案，我有一个特别的
suspect that we can i take a little
怀疑我们可以拿一点吗
speck I think because otherwise there's
我认为是斑点，因为否则
too many but we introduced about five
太多了，但我们介绍了大约五个
different new additions to the micro
微型的不同新增加
profile spec so it was it this is
个人资料规格，就是这个
actually kind of should have been maybe
实际上应该是
a tool because of the amount of stuff
由于数量太多而需要的工具
that was added so the previous one one
被添加，所以上一个
was was our baseline plus config and the
是我们的基准加上配置，
1.2 added about five new or four new
1.2增加了大约五个新的或四个新的
specifications my favorite amongst them
在其中我最喜欢的规格
is the JSON web token specification or
是JSON网络令牌规范，或者
the juvett they're called jots but
他们被称为笔记本
that's not actually possible to
这实际上是不可能的
pronunciate a W as an O but I guess
发音W为O，但我猜
maybe that's a new language thing and
也许这是一种新的语言，
I'm not aware of but anyway so that
我不知道但是无论如何
specification is great because one of
规格很棒，因为其中之一
the things that we haven't done
我们还没有做的事情
particularly well kind of an as an
特别好
enterprise community in Java is security
Java中的企业社区就是安全性
typically we have defined security as
通常，我们将安全性定义为
API calls inside the JVM and that
JVM内部的API调用以及
completely
完全地
NORs interoperability between servers in
NOR中服务器之间的互操作性
a portable way and with JSON web tokens
一种可移植的方式并带有JSON Web令牌
you can actually get that portability
您实际上可以获得这种可移植性
and so matters less what the API calls
因此，API调用的重要性降低了
are and matters a whole lot more
还有很多重要的事情
how can micro services and a distributed
微服务和分布式服务如何
architecture communicate in a stateless
体系结构无状态通信
way security across all those things and
所有这些事物的安全方式
so we have a pretty great specification
所以我们有一个很好的规范
for consuming JSON web tokens inside a
用于使用JSON Web令牌
micro service that's deployed in the
部署在
micro profile that allows you to have
微型配置文件，让您拥有
claims injected via at claim inside the
通过在内部的版权声明注入的版权声明
the beans and you can even say you know
豆子，你甚至可以说你知道
give me the current caller as a claim
给我当前的来电者作为索赔
you can get the whole JSON web token
您可以获取整个JSON Web令牌
injected in and inspect various things
注入并检查各种东西
you can use at rolls loud and have
你可以大声使用
permissions enforced and all this stuff
强制执行权限以及所有这些东西
is completely brand-new and I think it's
完全是全新的，我认为
pretty much gonna live for a very long
几乎可以活很久
time I don't really see anything
时间我什么都没看到
dethroning JSON web tokens anytime soon
尽快取消JSON Web令牌
so this would be great so this is a
所以这太好了，这是一个
architecture level compatibility that's
架构级别的兼容性
been added that's a new thing because
被添加是新事物，因为
the last time there was an architectural
上一次有建筑
compatibility for security it was called
所谓的安全兼容性
Corvo with CSI v2 and I don't think we
带CSI v2的Corvo，我认为我们不
want to be doing that anytime little
想一点点地做
thing little anecdotal last year at this
去年在这个小事
time at JavaOne
时间在JavaOne
we talked about okay what are the new
我们谈到了好吗
features we want to put in and this JWT
我们想要加入的功能和这个JWT
thing this was going to be okay we got
事情会好起来的，我们得到了
to do this and we got to do it quick
为此，我们必须快速完成
this will be real simple I don't know
这是非常简单的，我不知道
who said that and you know it took a
谁说的，你知道花了一个
collaborative effort I mean we got you
共同努力，我是说我们得到了你
know I know Red Hat team was driving it
知道我知道红帽团队正在开车
but we got input from a lot of different
但是我们得到了很多不同的意见
teams and you know what we finally
团队，你知道我们最终
produced is very good yeah I think the
制作的非常好，我认为
interesting thing is the way that
有趣的是
developed so Scott's dark seeded
发达，所以斯科特的黑暗种子
basically all the base all the you know
基本上所有的基础你都知道
foundation and then myself and John
基金会，然后是我自己和约翰
Ament came around and said you know you
阿曼特走了过来，说你认识你
can put dependency injection on that
可以把依赖注入
it'll be
这将是
pretty cool and then took on like a
很酷，然后像
whole nother level and the spec went you
整体水平和规格去了你
know a couple iterations after that we
在那之后我们知道了几次迭代
had people getting involved off of
让人们参与其中
Twitter so Hendrik eber's you know he he
Twitter，所以Hendrik eber是你知道他吗
followed a tweet where I said hey what
跟随一条推文，我说嘿
do you think about having in dependency
你认为有依赖吗
injection for claims and JSON web token
声明和JSON Web令牌注入
and suddenly he's on the mailing list
突然他在邮件列表中
and he submits a PR that day which is
他当天提交了PR
pretty cool and it got merged of course
很酷，它当然也合并了
because that's that's the way it is and
因为那是事实，
now his code is released here at JavaOne
现在他的代码在JavaOne上发布了
so that's an example of how quick things
这是一个快速的例子
move on on on that side of the fence so
在篱笆的那边继续前进
it's pretty neat I won't go to as much
整洁，我不会去太多
detail as David's just done sorry all
大卫的细节，对不起所有人
right
对
time wise one of the other things that
时间明智的其他事情之一
you know we've added to this release is
您知道我们已添加到此版本中的是
fault tolerance so starting to
容错性，所以开始
standardize things like circuit breakers
标准化断路器
etc that people have been using and in
人们一直在使用的等等
other technologies okay I'll also
其他技术好吧，我也会
mention one other unique thing we talked
提到我们谈论的另一件事
about with micah profile 1.1 that it was
关于micah配置文件1.1，这是
kind of a minor release and and we had
有点次要发行，而且我们有
config 1.0 and config by itself is a
config 1.0和config本身是一个
very positive addition the thing i want
非常积极的补充，我想要的东西
to point out with Mike profile 1.2 is
用Mike profile 1.2指出的是
that we had an update to that spec
我们已经对该规格进行了更新
already so it was only a couple of
所以已经只有几个
months later and one of our developers
几个月后，我们的一位开发人员
John Hammett he noticed you know a
约翰·哈米特（John Hammett），他注意到您知道
couple of things that we're missing from
我们缺少的几件事
config 1.0 and so he took ownership of
config 1.0，因此他获得了所有权
that spec and drove it in as config 1.1
该规范并将其作为配置1.1驱动
so there again it shows that not any one
所以又一次表明没有任何人
person or any one company owns any
个人或任何一家公司拥有任何
particular aspect of Micra profile we
我们Micra个人资料的特定方面
are sharing it among all of us and pick
在我们所有人中分享并选择
the ball up and moved it up a couple
球向上移动了几下
feet it was pretty great I was just
脚很棒，我只是
gonna mention that you know John Hammond
要提到你认识约翰·哈蒙德
isn't you know one of the you know
你不认识其中一个吗
employed by any of the big Java EE
受雇于任何大型Java EE
vendors right he's kind of just one of
供应商，他只是其中之一
the folks that kind of out in the crowd
那种在人群中出来的人
that decided that he was gonna go off
那决定他要离开
and build kind of his own implementation
并建立自己的实现方式
right so it's it's really cool he was
对，所以他真的很酷
here at JavaOne last year and I think he
去年在JavaOne上，我认为他
kind of fired up yeah this year he
今年有点被炒鱿鱼
wasn't able to make it but he sent
没能做到，但他发送了
another person from his team he's kind
他团队中的另一个人很友善
of generous like that and you know I
这样的慷慨，你知道我
think it's great that we have people
认为我们有很多人很棒
like John in the community and I think
像约翰在社区中一样，我认为
it's like a a sign of success that we
这就像是我们成功的标志
can't miss that within the first year of
不能错过第一年
micro profile there weren't just us as
微观概况不只是我们
implementations but people inspired to
实施，但人们受到启发
spend their spare time to build
花费业余时间建造
something and I know that may sound
我知道这听起来可能
small to spend your spare time to build
花费很少的时间来建立
something but Tommy was once a spare
但汤米曾经是个备用人
time and effort for me so you know who
我的时间和精力，所以你知道谁
knows what he's got to build in in in a
知道他必须在一个内建
couple years I think that that's awesome
几年我认为那很棒
that we're enabling that kind of thing
我们正在启用这种东西
and that he's really in there driving
他真的在那儿开车
the community all right hey Mikey
社区好吧，迈克
can you think of any other new specs yes
您能想到其他任何新规格吗？
I helped out with was metrics so one of
我帮助的是指标，所以其中之一
the things that I wanted to point out
我想指出的事情
with out was that it's fairly simple
没有的是，这很简单
spec from my background is not a
从我的背景规格不是
developer but a guy asked you know deal
开发人员，但有人问你知道交易
with the operations side of things I
在我的操作方面
think Jay MX is fantastic it's not in a
认为Jay MX很棒，它不在
amazingly easy to consume form a lot of
非常容易食用
people so that metric spec will expose a
人员，以便指标规格将暴露
couple of different rest endpoints which
几个不同的其余端点
are all standard across every
在每个方面都是标准的
implementation so you can predict
实施，因此您可以预测
without knowing ahead of time how this
事先不知道如何
other vendor has has configured things
其他供应商已经配置了东西
exactly what metrics you can get from
究竟可以从中获得什么指标
what end point which is pretty great but
哪个终点很棒
yeah just to echo the comments we've had
是的，只是为了回应我们已有的评论
before the the biggest thing that struck
在最大的事情发生之前
me about it was that I saw that metrics
我是因为我看到了这些指标
had already kind of started going and
已经有点开始了
took a look at it you know from my non
看看你从我的非知道
developer background and thought you
开发人员背景并以为你
know what
知道什么
I've got opinions and so I just kind of
我有意见，所以我只是
dived in and said hello I'm gonna be
潜水说你好我要成为
here now and I was pretty welcomed by
现在在这里，我受到了相当的欢迎
you know people from Red Hat and IBM and
您知道Red Hat和IBM的人以及
it was a lot of fun
很好玩
you know talking about my own experience
你知道我的经历
from working with different customers
与不同客户合作
who've had different requirements and
谁有不同的要求
you know obviously you feel really
你知道你显然感到
really listened to I found that the
真的听了，我发现
community itself and the people working
社区本身和工作人员
on it have been really really accepting
真的很接受
of someone who's not quite so technical
不太熟练的人
as the rest it's been good I wouldn't
其余的很好，我不会
describe this not technical you might be
描述这可能不是技术性的
selling yourself short on that one yeah
卖掉自己的那个耶
that's my get out of jail free card no
那是我脱离监狱的免费卡
that's that's my claim you can't take my
那就是我的主张，你不能接受我的
claim yeah do we get one last one yeah
声称是的，我们得到最后一个吗
health check so that that was a final
健康检查，以便最终
piece we had five new additions to Mike
我们为迈克增加了五个新成员
profile 1.2 so health check is just a
配置文件1.2，因此健康检查只是一个
very simple you know are you alive type
很简单，你知道你还活着吗
of check but it's you know okay I almost
支票，但你知道吗，我差不多
said standardized it but but it is you
说标准化，但这是你
know Specht out so that anyone who is
知道Specht出去，以便任何人
implementing this it would be consistent
实施这一点将是一致的
across all of their implementations I
在他们所有的实现中
guess I want to point out one little
我想指出一点
aspect that might be missed
可能遗漏的方面
health check enables people who are not
健康检查使那些不健康的人
micro profile implementations to
微观档案实施
interoperate with us so we're route
与我们进行互操作，以便我们前往
we're reaching out and touching cloud
我们正在伸出手并接触云
environments and saying here's how you
环境，并说这是你的方式
standardly get something from a micro
通常从微型设备上得到一些东西
profile implementation the JWT is the
JWT的配置文件实现是
same we're not the one producing the JWT
同样，我们不是生产JWT的人
it's gonna be API gateways and things
这将是API网关之类的东西
like that
像那样
key cloak and and various things and so
钥匙披风和各种东西等等
that's another example where we're
那是我们的另一个例子
integrating with standard cloud you know
与您知道的标准云集成
tech and it's it's always health I mean
科技，这就是永远健康
you know we aren't the one aggregating
你知道我们不是一个聚集的人
the health data so we're really directly
健康数据，所以我们真的是直接
and deliberately integrating with
并故意与
various aspects of cloud which is
云的各个方面是
something that can't be missed we're not
不能错过的东西我们不是
just creating in our space we're
只是在我们的空间中创造
connecting to outside our space right so
连接到我们的空间之外，所以
I'm gonna switch gears here a little bit
我要在这里换档
and now talk about Java EE and this is
现在谈论Java EE，这是
opportunity perhaps for for David to
大卫也许有机会
talk to us about what's new in Java you
与我们讨论Java的新功能
know EE 8 and then we can kind of bring
知道EE 8，然后我们可以带来
it all together a little bit yeah so
在一起一点是的，所以
first I just want to show you this this
首先我只想给你看这个
is the Oracle several statements so as
是Oracle的几条语句，因此
you know we have released a Java eight
你知道我们发布了Java 8
21st of September so a few days ago one
9月21日，所以几天前
of the things that we did in Java yet is
我们在Java中所做的事情是
basically the alignment which are ic8 so
基本上是ic8的对齐方式
wherever we can we have a
只要我们能有一个
the API to leverage the new stuff that
API利用新的东西
we had in a CLI like some basic stuff
我们在CLI中有一些基本知识
GPA now support date and time API GSN
GPA现在支持日期和时间API GSN
also support date and time API now we
现在也支持日期和时间API
also did quite a few nice things
也做了很多不错的事情
regarding for example compression stage
关于压缩阶段
API I think so that concurrent thing
我认为API是并发的东西
that gives you the ability to have a
让您有能力
sync task execution in Jack's arrest now
立即同步Jack逮捕中的任务执行
we have an reactive I think invoker that
我认为我们有一个反应性的调用者
allows you to basically compose multiple
基本上可以让您撰写多个
services invocation in a very specific
非常具体的服务调用
fashion and all of that in an icing
时尚和所有这些锦上添花
fashion CDI - so CDI - as now the
时尚CDI-如此CDI-像现在一样
support for a synchronous event and
支持同步事件和
guess what a synchronous events of CDI -
猜猜CDI的同步事件是什么-
also support the completion stage api of
还支持的完成阶段api
java SE 8 so basically whenever we can
Java SE 8所以基本上只要我们可以
we have updated the spec to make sure
我们已经更新了规格以确保
that java c 8 can be leveraged now
现在可以利用Java C 8
something which we have done which is
我们所做的是
also quite nice is we have basically
也很好，我们基本上
fixed the design support that was
修复了当时的设计支持
started - introducing July 7 so you know
开始-介绍7月7日，所以您知道
in Java 7 we had we have this JSONP 1.0
在Java 7中，我们拥有这个JSONP 1.0
api which was which is quite nice but it
的API，这是相当不错的，但它
was not complete
不完整
now with that new Jason B API so we have
现在有了新的Jason B API，所以我们有了
a complete end-to-end a binding story
完整的端到端绑定故事
for Jason so that's something which is
对于杰森，那是
also very welcome
也很欢迎
something else is select for servlet for
为servlet选择了其他东西
not a lot I mean from the outside not a
我的意思不是很多，不是从外面
lot of new stuff but on 100 the hood
很多新东西，但引擎盖上有100个
servlet 4 brings HTTP to support to the
Servlet 4将HTTP支持
platform so that's something that I
平台，这就是我
think is very nice and something that
觉得很好，还有一些
will will hold use over time and I mean
会随着时间的推移保持使用状态，我的意思是
so that's basically some of the things
所以这基本上是一些事情
that we have done I forgot to mention so
我们所做的我忘了提
you've talked about GWT in Java 8 will
您已经讨论过Java 8中的GWT
we have also added a new security API so
我们还添加了一个新的安全性API，因此
basically we are trying to finally solve
基本上我们正在努力最终解决
simplify how you can apply security
简化如何应用安全性
concern in a java application so that's
在Java应用程序中关注的问题是
the first step but I think that's a
第一步，但我认为那是
welcome step in the direction so then to
欢迎朝这个方向走，然后
kind of bring these bring it all
带来这些带来一切
together and this is an open-ended
在一起，这是一个开放式的
question to anybody
向任何人提问
how might micro profile accelerate the
微观概况如何促进
adoption of Java EE 8 because that's you
采用Java EE 8的原因在于
know the kind of the title of the panels
知道面板名称的种类
or the sessions I'm very interested
或我非常感兴趣的会议
and what people's thoughts are there
还有人们的想法
I'll jump in first so I think one of the
我先跳，所以我认为
things that you know we were pushing
你知道我们在推动的事情
very heavily when we kicked off micro
当我们开始微的时候非常沉重
profile was that you know the perception
个人资料是你知道感知
that app servers in general are not
一般而言，应用服务器不是
conducive to building micro services is
有利于建立微服务
you know it's not really accurate we've
你知道我们不是很准确
had very lightweight app servers from a
从一个非常轻量级的应用服务器
number of vendors over the years and you
多年来的供应商数量，您
know you don't actually need to strip
知道你实际上不需要剥离
down your your monolithic application
降低您的整体应用程序
server to get a runtime that actually is
服务器获取实际上是
you know quite small a lot of app server
你知道很多应用服务器
vendors produce application servers that
供应商生产的应用服务器
are let's say e 7 compliant that were
假设我们符合e 7
pretty nimble it really boot fast very
它非常灵巧，启动速度非常快
small memory footprint I think with ee8
我认为ee8占用的内存较小
we should see exactly the same thing and
我们应该看到完全一样的东西，
I would like to believe that micro
我想相信
profile one three one four whatever will
剖一三一四随便
you know start to address yet support
你知道开始解决，但仍然支持
pull in some of the you know newer
拉一些你知道较新的
features that David's just talked about
大卫刚刚谈到的功能
and drive ee8 adoption maybe not
并推动ee8的采用可能不会
necessarily explicit you know people
一定很明确，你认识的人
hopefully will start to deploy micro
希望将开始部署微型
profile I say 1.4 compatible
我说1.4兼容的配置文件
applications and just not necessarily
应用程序，但不一定
need to know they're running e 8 an app
需要知道他们正在运行一个应用程序e 8
server underneath the covers I think
我认为服务器在掩护之下
that's that's a really good thing for
那对我来说真的是一件好事
micro profile and a really good thing
微观轮廓，真是一件好事
for Java EE I guess I would add that you
对于Java EE，我想我会补充一点
know it probably would be a bit of time
知道可能会有点时间
before we see you know obviously with
在我们看到您明显与
with EE 4j another major revision we'll
对于EE 4j，我们将进行另一个重大修订
be doing a lot of transitioning of stuff
做很多事情的过渡
and as that that happens we'll be still
那样的话，我们将保持静止
doing releases of micro profile they all
他们都在发布微轮廓
work on top of an EE container and so
在EE容器上工作等等
any gaps that need to be filled between
之间需要填补的任何空白
now and when we get e4j really moving
现在，当我们让e4j真正动起来时
quickly
很快
well micro profile is there to pick up
微观概况在那里
the slack and in the meantime and so
松弛，与此同时等等
that you know that's a great asset to to
你知道这是一个伟大的资产
all of us
我们所有人
and so I think that that that can't be
所以我认为那不可能
missed that you know the pace that what
错过了你知道什么节奏
we've been going and micro profile has
我们去了，微观概况
actually been increasing if you look at
实际上，如果你看
the time between the one oh and the one
一次到一次之间的时间
point one speck it was I want to say
我想说的是一点
nine months or something along those
九个月左右
lines you know yeah but there was the
行，你知道是的，但是有
migration to eclipse oh yeah I mean we
迁移到日食哦，是的，我们是
did take some time yeah well we did the
确实花了一些时间，是的，我们做到了
migration to eclipse just as EE for J is
迁移到Eclipse，就像EE for J一样
gonna have to do the migration for
必须要做的迁移
Eclipse and of course we're all going to
Eclipse，当然我们都要做
help because that's that's what open
帮助，因为那是开放的
source means but our pace picked up
资料来源，但我们的步伐加快了
pretty quickly so so between one point
很快，所以在一点之间
one and one point to where they were
一分一指他们在哪里
released in the same quarter which is a
在同一季度发布
really great thing you know but part of
你知道的很棒的事情，但是一部分
that was because we decided I'm doing
那是因为我们决定我在做
you know a time boxed release and you
你知道一个盒装发行，你
know when one point one was coming out
知道什么时候一点一出来
we determined that okay
我们确定可以
we had these other ones already in the
我们已经在其他这些
works but they just weren't ready to
可以，但是他们还没有准备好
release yet so I said okay no we're only
发布了，所以我说好吧不，我们只是
gonna go with config and we had some
要去配置，我们有一些
questions about okay but it's only
关于还可以的问题，但这仅仅是
config and it's like yeah but doesn't
配置，就像是，但不是
matter that's the way that we're going
这就是我们要走的路
to do it so then we had another time box
这样做，然后我们有了另一个时间框
release for Java one and that's where we
Java版本之一，这就是我们
had the other you know all five of the
有另一个你知道所有五个
other features ready to go clearly some
准备就绪的其他功能
motivated people to make Java one way as
激励人们将Java作为一种方式
what's called conference driven
所谓的会议驱动
development exactly this submit a talk
发展正本就此发表演讲
to do something that you want to create
做你想创造的东西
yep that date will eventually come oh
是的，那个日子最终会来的哦
gosh oh gosh let's make it and just a
天哪，哦，让我们做到这一点，只是一个
quick mention if you look at open JDK
如果您看一下开放的JDK，请快速提及
OpenJDK is also moving to that industry
OpenJDK也正在向该行业发展
hi you know maybe it was a good idea
嗨，你知道也许这是个好主意
yeah I know I think it's a good thing
是的，我知道我认为这是一件好事
yeah one of the neat things that we
是的，我们整洁的事情之一
should you know begin thinking about is
你应该知道开始考虑的是
since everyone kind of has these tiny
因为每个人都有这些微小的
box releases and acts is actually trying
盒子释放和行为实际上是在尝试
to align what we do with you know
使我们所做的与您了解一致
eventually the e4j and with micro
最终是e4j和微型
profile along with what's happening with
个人资料以及正在发生的事情
Java SE right and see if we can begin
Java SE正确，看看我们是否可以开始
kind of lining up the features up the
将功能排列在一起
stack to take advantage of the things
堆叠以利用事物
that are happening
发生了
in the stack I think there would be a
在堆栈中，我认为会有一个
really neat thing for us to be able to
我们能够做到的整洁的事情
do with time box releases I think it'll
与时间盒发布有关，我认为
make us more able to do that yeah I
让我们更有能力做到这一点，我
would say to make that point even louder
会说使这一点更大声
eight is Java SE eight so that's a whole
八个是Java SE八个，所以整个
major job of revision behind obviously
修订的主要工作明显落后
there was no real other choice because
没有其他选择，因为
you know it was difficult to develop ee8
你知道很难开发ee8
on top of se nine because things were
在九点之上，因为事情是
kind of in flux but with basically
有点变化，但基本上
six-month releases of se there's no
se的六个月发行没有
reason that we would be even you know
我们甚至会成为你的原因
more than six months behind that I can
我可以落后六个多月
see us being six months behind that but
看到我们落后了六个月，但
wouldn't be you know like a whole year
你会不会像整整一年
behind that alright let's see I'm sorry
好吧，让我们看看对不起
quick time check here to do to do okay
快速时间检查这里要做的事
so here's a here's another question how
所以这是另一个问题
may ye forge a and micro profile both
可能会伪造和微观轮廓
big Eclipse projects aligned in the
大型Eclipse项目与
future so I'm gonna tee David up for
未来，所以我要戴维准备
this because we we had a we had a two
这是因为我们有一个我们有两个
hour meeting not about this particular
小时会议不是关于这个特殊的
topic but it did come up there was a few
话题，但确实出现了一些
people expressed how they reference they
人们表达了他们如何参考他们
expressed how they thought micro profile
表达了他们如何看待微观形象
and e4j should come together if at all
和e4j应该一起走
and I think we all agree that David kind
我想我们都同意大卫善良
of put it more succinctly now I have to
现在我必须更简洁地说
remember my exact words well I guess I
记得我的确切话我想我
would see that ideally in my perspective
在我看来，理想情况下
and I guess some other people think the
我猜有些人认为
same and we'll see once we talk about it
一样，一旦我们谈论它，我们将看到
in a list but I I can would like to see
在列表中，但II希望看到
micro profile come under the e4j
微型配置文件位于e4j下
umbrella kind of as the innovative edge
雨伞有点像创新的优势
where we can incubate and experiment
在这里我们可以进行孵化和实验
with some good ideas and then you know
有一些好的想法，然后你知道
have that continue to be kind of the
有那种继续
innovative you know engine it's being
你知道引擎正在创新
right now but inside the e4j umbrella
现在，但在e4j雨伞内
and if if I get my way I would love to
如果我愿意的话，我很乐意
someday be able to say you know a micro
有一天可以说你知道一个微
profile that would sort of be fun
个人资料会很有趣
a new name yeah exactly so that that
是一个新名字，就是这样
would be really cool I think that would
真的很酷，我认为
be like you know I would be dying to
就像你知道我会死的
tweet that the day that if it might
鸣叫那一天，如果可能的话
someday become real so so maybe I can
有一天变得真实，所以也许我可以
make a comment even though I'm not
即使我不发表评论
making any forward statement so so if we
做出任何前瞻性声明，所以如果我们
look today we basically have two well
看今天我们基本上有两个好
two things so we have Java 8 which was
两件事，所以我们有了Java 8
just released and we have micro profiles
刚刚发布，我们有微观概况
so you already have multiple release and
所以您已经有多个版本
we are just starting to work on that e4j
我们才刚刚开始在该e4j上工作
migration so we know that well you have
迁移，所以我们知道你有
you have gone through that exercise so
你已经完成了这个练习，所以
we know that it's not a simple exercise
我们知道这不是一个简单的练习
to move such a project because it's a
移动这样的项目，因为它是一个
very large project to the kids
对孩子们来说非常大的项目
foundation so I think that shot will
基础，所以我认为拍摄会
well we really have to focus on on those
好吧，我们真的必须专注于那些
two I mean II Java e8 and micro profile
两个我的意思是II Java e8和micro profile
and hopefully over time yet there will
并希望随着时间的流逝
be some convergence between the two but
两者之间有些融合，但是
let's not anticipate that too much and
我们不要期望太多
already talking now about that
现在已经在谈论这个
conversion I think it's a bit too early
转换我认为还为时过早
I would also add that you know
我还要补充一点，你知道
ultimately onesie 4j is out there this
最终onesie 4j在那里
is something that we would discuss with
是我们要讨论的东西
both communities this is not something
两个社区都不是
that Red Hat
那顶红帽子
Oracle IBM or whoever is going to decide
Oracle IBM或将要决定的任何人
this is something that the communities
这是社区
have to decide if the communities decide
必须决定社区是否决定
they want to keep the status quo two
他们想保持现状
completely separate projects then that's
完全独立的项目，那就是
how we're gonna do it yeah I'll state
我们要怎么做，我会说
that I'm speaking for myself and I'm
我在为自己说话，我在
historically very excitable so yeah take
历史上非常令人兴奋，所以
that but but the fact that both project
那，但事实是，两个项目
are and will be under the Kids
现在并将在儿童之下
Foundation I mean will greatly simplify
我的意思是说基金会将大大简化
those discussion and that potential
那些讨论和那种潜力
conventions just to clarify because you
约定只是为了澄清，因为您
know people in the audience may not know
知道听众中的人可能不知道
currently micro profile is under a
目前，微观资料处于
different top-level project were under
正在进行不同的顶级项目
the technology project in Eclipse and
Eclipse中的技术项目
for e4j we are establishing a new
对于e4j，我们正在建立一个新的
top-level project called e4j so
顶层项目称为e4j，因此
currently they would be in separate
目前他们将分开
projects and that's why the discussion
项目，这就是为什么讨论
excuse me the discussion would have to
对不起，讨论将不得不
happen eventually you know are we going
最终发生，你知道我们要去
to move them under the same project or
将它们移到同一项目下，或
are we going to keep them separate so
我们要把它们分开吗
something down the road and that's where
道路上的东西，那就是
we love to hear feedback on anything
我们喜欢听到任何反馈
right new specs you know process things
您知道正确的新规格要处理的事情
how do we develop you know release
我们如何发展您知道的发行版
cycles going forward anything that has
循环前进的任何东西
to do with you know moving the you know
与你知道有关移动你知道的
enterprise Java EE forward or ie 4j
企业Java EE转发或4j
forward is like really good feedback I
前锋就像真的反馈很好
really want to do that oh someone forgot
真的很想这么做哦，有人忘了
to mention we also have an EE forge a
提到我们也有一个EE伪造的
commuter the mailing list right in the
将邮件列表通勤
Eclipse Foundation so go to the Eclipse
Eclipse Foundation，所以去Eclipse
Foundation and join the EEE - EEE forge
建立并加入EEE-EEE伪造
a - community alias and you know just if
一个-社区别名，您知道
you want to catch up it's not that deep
你想赶上它不是那么深
in terms because it was just set up you
因为它只是建立你
can get caught up really quickly and
可以很快被赶上
then just contribute now are there any
那现在就贡献一下
questions from folks in the audience
听众的提问
raise your hands and I can bring around
举起你的手，我可以带走
bring around a mic if you have any easy
如果方便的话，带上麦克风
questions tough questions so does Mike
问难题，迈克也问
report this micro profile follow the
报告此微型个人资料，请按照
same pattern as Java is having a one
与Java具有相同的模式
spec in multiple implementations all of
在多种实现中的规范
you guys including the same jar files on
你们包括相同的jar文件
your your app servers or what have you
您的应用服务器或您拥有什么
so no we each have our own
所以不，我们每个人都有自己的
implementations so in micro profile we
实施，所以在微观概况
are defining a spec a specification an
正在定义规范和规范
API and a TCK the implementations we do
API和TCK我们执行的实现
not define a reference implementation
没有定义参考实现
there may be some sample implementations
可能会有一些示例实现
created but there's no reference
已创建，但没有参考
implementation each of the vendors
实施每个供应商
create their own implementation of the
创建自己的实现
specifications but but there isn't
规格，但没有
anything to prevent multiple vendors
任何防止多个供应商的东西
collaborating on the same bit of code
在相同的代码上进行协作
that then gets deployed into there you
然后被部署到你那里
know compliant implementation so we just
知道合规的实现，所以我们只是
didn't mandate it we kind of good
没有强制要求我们很好
open-source practice let the communities
开源实践让社区
decide what they want to do yeah like
决定他们想做什么
for example how mark is probably going
例如标记可能如何进行
to share the same config a API
共享相同的配置API
implementation that Tommy does just
Tommy所做的实现
because John met and is a very big
因为约翰遇见了，而且非常大
Apache guy and so are we so we're doing
Apache的家伙，我们也是这样
implementation over there and then we'll
实施，然后我们将
compile consume it in hammock will
编译在吊床上消费它会
consume it in Tommy and so there's
在汤米吃掉它，所以有
nothing preventing sharing but it's not
没有什么可以阻止共享，但不是
mandated now you got a complex question
现在要求您有一个复杂的问题
now that you've bought it yourself yeah
现在您已经自己购买了
okay so any other questions raise your
好吧，所以任何其他问题都会引起您
hand I think for from the perspective of
我从以下角度考虑
accelerating the adoption perspective
加快采用角度
see currently all ye like the
看到目前所有你们都喜欢
installation or implementation that is
安装或实施
out there like the actual production
像实际生产一样
application that are out there how is
那里的应用程序如何
there any plan to basically provide some
有什么计划可以基本上提供一些
type of like a conversion or some type
像是转化类型或某种类型
of way of enabling your existing
使您现有的方式
application to go on the on the micro
申请继续进行
service architecture type scenery that
服务架构类型的风景
can use either microphone or or the e4j
可以使用麦克风或e4j
I'll make it a simple answer and I'm
我会简单回答，
sure it's probably similar for everybody
确保每个人都可能相似
we don't plan to have a separate ee
我们不打算有单独的ee
Tommy and a separate micro profile Tommy
汤米（Tommy）和一个单独的微型档案（Tommy）
we're putting everything together and so
我们把所有东西都放在一起
you have access to the standard EE stuff
您可以使用标准的EE工具
plus you can get additional micro
另外，您可以获得更多的微型
profile api's they're ready to use
他们已经可以使用个人资料api了
should you want them so you don't really
你应该不要他们吗？
have to install anything more in order
必须安装更多东西才能
to do that and and and of course
为此，并且当然
everybody will probably do things
每个人都可能会做事
differently but you know that that's how
不同，但是你知道那就是
that's how we've decided to incorporate
这就是我们决定合并的方式
both EE and micro profile in the same
EE和微观配置文件都在同一位置
box because they do complement each
框，因为它们确实互补
other they're not conflicting in any way
其他他们没有任何冲突
so so micro profile technologies are you
所以你是微轮廓技术
know in addition to a lot of the EE
除了很多EE知道
stuff now micro profile mandates only a
现在，微型个人资料仅授权一个
few things but there's nothing stopping
几件事，但没有停止
you from putting more things in the box
您从盒子里放了更多东西
and so that's the way we've we've we've
所以这就是我们拥有的方式
attempted to do it
试图做到
I don't know if you guys want to give
我不知道你们是否愿意付出
your perspectives on how you enable
您对如何启用的观点
people to use both so you know we have a
人们同时使用两者，所以您知道我们有一个
project called wild fly swarm soon be
名为“野生苍蝇群”的项目即将成为现实
product called wild fly swarm which is
被称为野蝇群的产品
our micro profile compliant
符合我们的微资料
implementation is based on wild fly our
实现是基于我们的野性飞
app server and you know at least at the
应用服务器，您至少知道
moment it's essentially you know you
此刻基本上是你知道你
take your full EE application server and
带上完整的EE应用程序服务器，
you know you can pare it back using
你知道你可以用
various tools that ship with with swarm
群附带的各种工具
to get just the bare minimum we cut I
为了得到我们所削减的最低限度
don't think we'd kinda Sturm but we we
不要以为我们有点Sturm，但我们
call it right sizing the app server but
称它为正确的应用服务器大小，但
because it's compliant with micro
因为它符合micro
profile we or has compliant
符合我们或符合要求的个人资料
configurations for micro profile we can
微型配置文件的配置，我们可以
guarantee that you can still you know
保证你仍然可以知道
port your application from you know one
从您知道的移植您的应用程序
from our implementation to you know the
从我们的实施到您知道
Tommy tribe implementation or even to
汤米部落的实施甚至
the IBM implementation but I did want to
IBM实施，但我确实想
ask I wondered whether your question was
问我想知道你的问题是否
more about how if you starting with an
有关如何从头开始的更多信息
application so a full Java EE
完整的Java EE应用程序
application server do you start down the
应用服务器，您是否启动了
journey to to right-size your deployment
正确确定部署大小的旅程
to only have those things in it that you
只把那些东西放在里面
need for the business logic I don't know
需要我不知道的业务逻辑
if that was it yeah I think where
如果是的话，我想在哪里
question one was from the existing so
问题之一是从现有的
the existing application that already
现有的应用程序已经
has the e spec like you have you have
具有您所拥有的电子规格
JSP you have a JB's MD B's and all those
JSP，您拥有JB的MD B和所有这些
things how do you map those into if into
事情如何将这些映射到
a micro profile or ej like is there any
微观档案或ej，例如
type of recommended way or some type of
推荐方式的类型或某种
conversion or analysis tool or something
转换或分析工具之类的东西
that can be used to to create that
可以用来创建那个
migration path so as so if I have an
迁移路径，如果我有一个
application I wanted to go more on that
我想在此方面做更多的应用
path how what's the path towards that
路径是怎么回事
well first of all I'd I'd say don't
首先我要说不要
necessarily have to buy into micro
一定要买入微
services now everything has to be a
服务，现在一切都必须是
micro service if you've got and I have a
微服务，如果您有，我有一个
Java EE application
Java EE应用程序
that is running really well for you
对你来说真的很好
today why would you want to change that
今天你为什么要改变那个
so just because lots of other people are
所以只是因为很多其他人
saying you should use microservices
说你应该使用微服务
doesn't actually mean that you need to
实际上并不意味着您需要
use micro-services if you do decide to
如果您决定使用微服务
go down that route currently you know in
沿着那条目前你知道的路线走
micro profile I don't think we have any
微型个人资料，我认为我们没有任何资料
best practices or recommendations that's
最佳做法或建议
certainly something that I think you
当然是我认为你的事情
know certainly the message in the
当然知道
meeting we were talking about earlier we
开会，我们刚才在谈论
we probably start to need to start
我们可能需要开始
thinking about there are things that I
想着我有的事
could say but from a RedHat point of
可以说，但是从RedHat的角度来看
view bright I think I want to keep this
查看明亮我想我要保持这个
kind of micro profile neutral so no I
那种中性的微轮廓，所以没有我
think what and I guess I would just
想什么，我想我只是
stress again I think the mapping concept
再次强调，我认为映射概念
is maybe either you don't have to change
也许你不必改变
anything you just you know for I know
你所知道的一切，因为我知道
you want to stay generic but it's a hard
您想保持通用性，但是很难
to answer the question so like if you
回答问题，就像你
are Tommy user you just keep upgrading
是Tommy用户，您只是继续升级
and you will eventually start getting
然后你最终会开始
more and more in micro profile stuff you
越来越多的微型个人资料中
don't the change or map or modify your
不要更改或映射或修改您的
app just there's eventually going to be
应用程序，最终将是
more and more things for you to use so
越来越多的东西供您使用
there's no there's no rip and replace
没有撕裂和更换
you know it's just keep going down the
你知道那只是继续下去
EE path and more micro profile things
EE路径和更多微型配置文件
will start to show up in the same binary
将开始以相同的二进制文件显示
and you don't have to do anything if you
而且如果您不需要做任何事情
don't want to or you can start using
不想，或者您可以开始使用
this stuff if you'd like just one thing
如果您只想一件事
to add though is that we made the
要补充的是，我们做了
decision quite early on because that
很早就做出决定，因为
microphone was going to be from JDK 8 so
麦克风将来自JDK 8，所以
I hope you're not still on JDK 7 but if
我希望您还没有使用JDK 7，但是如果
you are you would need to move to JDK 8
您将需要转到JDK 8
yeah that would be very very good
是的，那将非常非常好
call-out
大喊
and one thing I'll add is you know
我要补充的一件事是你知道
different vendors are approaching this
不同的供应商正在接近
problem in different ways right we all
我们以不同的方式解决问题
kind of approach the idea of even
一种方法甚至
application servers Lee's just just even
应用服务器李的只是
take Michael profile out of it right
从迈克尔的个人资料中脱颖而出
it's it's we all kind of have whether
是我们所有人都有
it's not you know different module
不是你知道不同的模块
implementations or you know a single
实现，或者您只知道一个
kind of deployable runtime you know we
你知道我们可以部署的运行时
all kind of take different approaches
各种采取不同的方法
and we just I think naturally extend
我们只是自然而然地
that into our micro profile
进入我们的微观资料
implementation so all right is this the
实施，所以这是正确的
hard one don't disappoint how do you
努力一点，不要让你失望
solve world hunger with micro profile go
用微轮廓解决世界饥饿问题
so I'm assuming that since Java EE 8 is
所以我假设因为Java EE 8是
fairly new you guys coated your specs
你们是新手，他们介绍了您的规格
against Java EE 7 now there are some
针对Java EE 7现在有一些
Java EE specs including micro profile so
Java EE规范包括微概要文件
it's a CDI JSONP and and jax-rs so if I
这是一个CDI JSONP和jax-rs，所以如果我
have a Java EE eight implementation and
有一个Java EE 8实现，并且
I want to go something against micro
我想反对微
profile can I use Java EE 8 features yes
配置文件我可以使用Java EE 8功能吗
okay we did we put that in as a base to
好吧，我们做了，以此为基础
say that like we identified CDI 1.2 as
就像我们将CDI 1.2确定为
the minimum okay so if you're moving up
最低限度，所以如果您要向上移动
and using CDI 2.0 then you can go ahead
然后使用CDI 2.0，那么您可以继续
and do that but all of our
并做到这一点，但我们所有人
implementations and relationship among
实现和之间的关系
all the features may be you know there
所有功能可能都在那里
there's some aspects of the new features
新功能的某些方面
that we want to take advantage of so we
我们想利用的优势，所以我们
are looking at a new update to the
正在寻找新的更新
release and this is where we're thinking
发布，这就是我们在想的地方
about updating the the numbering scheme
关于更新编号方案
so for micro file 2x then we would
因此对于微型文件2x，我们将
update our base set of features to Java
将基本功能集更新为Java
EE 8 right and then at that time we're
正确的EE 8，那时我们
also talking about bringing in JSON B to
还谈到将JSON B引入
complement the JSON P we waited a long
补充了我们等待了很长时间的JSON P
time for Java EE a so we really want to
Java EE的时间，所以我们真的很想
use the new features a good answer yeah
使用新功能是一个很好的答案
I mean basically the spec or if you look
我的意思是基本上规格或如果您看
at the micro profile 1.2 spec it's not
在Micro Profile 1.2规范中，它不是
long so it
很久了
very easy to read it says in the CGI
在CGI中非常容易阅读
section specifically the implementation
本节具体执行
is required yet minimum to do you know
是必需的，但至少要知道吗
1.2 but if it wants to do 2.0 that's
1.2，但如果它想做2.0，那就是
okay it you may sacrifice some
好吧，你可能会牺牲一些
portability be a smart user and go have
可移植性成为一个聪明的用户，并拥有
fun in the upcoming micro profile list
即将到来的微型个人资料列表中的乐趣
it's like standardization of dupage our
就像标准化dupage一样
tour or application service doing things
旅游服务或应用服务
all differently still not at the moment
现在一切都不同了
no no at the moment we all have our own
不，不，目前我们都有自己的
different approaches to you know how you
不同的方法让你知道你如何
create your Ruby jar yeah well I mean
创建您的Ruby jar是的，我的意思是
maybe we might get together and try and
也许我们可能会聚在一起尝试
stand out some aspects of that at some
在某些方面脱颖而出
point but I don't think it's a critical
点，但我认为这不是关键
thing at this stage yeah I would simply
在这个阶段的事情是的，我只是
say that when we started the conference
说当我们开始会议时
application you know the it's kind of a
您知道的应用程序
reference architecture and for those who
参考架构，适合那些
aren't familiar with it
不熟悉
basically and we we got started and we
基本上，我们开始了，我们
said let's do a sample app and then we
说让我们做一个示例应用程序，然后我们
stopped herself dead in the tracks and
让自己死在铁轨上
say wait how can you have a
说等等你怎么能有一个
microservices architecture with one app
一个应用程序的微服务架构
so so we had four micro services and
所以我们有四个微服务
they deploy on all the servers and they
他们部署在所有服务器上，
all have uber jar in it everyone's uber
每个人都有超级罐子
jar started out with different flags you
Jar开始时带有不同的标志
know on how to configure the ports but
知道如何配置端口，但是
to kind of have started to become a
已经开始成为一种
little bit more mmm lined up I guess
我想更多一点
and so the conference app does show you
因此会议应用程序确实向您显示
how to do over jar and all the
如何做罐子和所有
implementations that are up here so it's
在这里的实现
not standard but it's kind of de facto
不是标准的，但实际上
Inge you know it's becoming a little
英格，你知道它正在变得有点
kind of de-facto ish possible to do with
事实可能与
everybody I'm on a related note there
大家我都在相关的笔记上
was a suggestion by John Hammond he's
是约翰·哈蒙德（John Hammond）的建议，
quite busy yeah so he suggested having
是的，很忙，所以他建议有
common configuration options so maybe
常见的配置选项，所以也许
you could set micro profile HTTP deport
您可以设置微配置文件HTTP逐出
or HTTP port and it
或HTTP端口及其
the same for each that was mentioned in
提到的每一个都一样
our in our deluxe Belgium talk yeah last
我们在豪华比利时的谈话中是的
November yeah so it's it's cropped began
是的，是十一月
I think recently on their mailing list
我认为最近在他们的邮件列表上
artists or I mention of it so that there
艺术家或我提到它，以便在那里
wasn't many people kind of giving John
不是很多人都会给约翰
much feedback on that so I thought maybe
对此有很多反馈，所以我想也许
it's not so wanted but if it's something
它不是很想要，但如果有的话
that's appeals t then you know get
那很吸引人，那么你知道得到
involved on the mailing list and I'm
参与邮件列表，我
sure you're gonna be happy to do another
确保您会乐于再做
check Thanks yeah you are the phone to
检查谢谢，是您的电话
microphone poor file basically as kind
麦克风差档基本上一样
of as well standard let's put that way
以及标准的，让我们这样
for doing micro services all right but
可以做微服务
so you started at the bare minimum and
所以你从最低限度开始
now you are starting to add more and
现在您开始添加更多和
more stuff to that affair but at some
还有更多的东西，但有些
point it's the microphone file itself
指向麦克风文件本身
might not be exactly Michael anymore
可能不再是迈克尔了
right so is there any plan to also then
对，所以有什么计划可以
make things like option the future is
使诸如期权之类的事情成为未来
there at some point where you say okay
在某个地方你说还可以
no we we have to stop because it's not
不，我们必须停止，因为这不是
really Michael I know so one
真的迈克尔，我知道
clarification is that the micro profile
澄清的是，微观轮廓
the micro part was meant for micro
微观部分是为微观
services so it it could grow but the
服务，使其可以增长，但
other thing even though we are defining
即使我们正在定义
micro profile releases each of the
微观个人资料会释放每个
features that feed into that are
提供的功能是
independent so if a given implementation
独立的，所以如果给定的实现
does not want to for whatever reason
不想出于任何原因
they don't want to implement the full
他们不想实施全部
micro profile 1.2 or 1.3 they could pick
可以选择的微型配置文件1.2或1.3
the individual features that they want
他们想要的个人功能
to implement so you know if there is you
实施，以便您知道是否有您
know size concerns or resource concerns
知道大小或资源问题
whatever it is in order to to provide
为了提供任何东西
that capability
这种能力
you could subdivide the phone like a
您可以像
profile release and I mean we're not
个人资料发布，我的意思是我们不是
requiring any particular implementation
需要任何特定的实现
that has to move up to the next release
必须升级到下一个版本
so you know you can have a micro profile
所以你知道你可以有一个微型个人资料
compliant one-oh implementation and
符合一一实施
stick it one out that's what you like or
坚持下去就是你想要的
one one you don't have to move to 1/2 or
一个你不必移动到1/2或
1/3 or 1/4 it's not it's not like a
不是1/3还是1/4
software release where you don't get
无法获得的软件版本
support for the previous version once
一次支持以前的版本
the new version comes out
新版本问世
and one thing I would like to see I've
我想看到的一件事是
talked about this on the mailing list a
在邮件列表中谈到了这一点
few times but maybe it's a little bit
几次，但也许有点
too complex at this stage I actually
在这个阶段我太复杂了
think some kind of tree light model for
想一些树光模型
how releases branch off each other might
释放如何相互分离
be more applicable than the linear
比线性更适用
approach we're currently doing but you
我们目前正在做的方法，但您
gotta start somewhere so I think it's
必须从某个地方开始，所以我认为
it's not necessarily the fact that micro
不一定是微观的事实
profile as we add more and more things
随着我们添加越来越多的东西
will require more and more components to
将需要越来越多的组件来
be in the you know the stack as you
在你知道你的堆栈
actually implement it so I actually I
实际上实施它，所以我实际上我
actually have a question yet to testing
其实还有一个问题要测试
so here's my tiptoes okay so it kinda
所以这是我的脚尖好吗
came up a couple of times now about
现在大约出现了几次
standards right and in the industry kind
标准权和行业种类
of you know perceives the JCP is a
你们知道JCP是
standards organization so maybe this is
标准组织，所以也许这是
a question it's a question for everyone
一个问题，这是每个人的问题
but but maybe I'll kind of start out
但也许我会开始
with David is with EE for Jay and the
与David在一起的是Jay和EE的EE
Eclipse Foundation do we kind of is that
Eclipse Foundation我们要做的是
do you think consider standard or or how
您认为考虑标准还是
you know well yeah maybe I'll just leave
你知道的，是的，也许我就走了
it that you should people consider this
人们应该考虑这个
to be a standard or whatever you know
成为标准或任何你知道的
other people can can pipe in as well
其他人也可以通过管道
it's it's not simple to answer but one
这不是简单的答案，而是一个
of the reason why we have moved well why
为什么我们前进的原因
we have decided to move java development
我们已经决定迁移Java开发
to an open source foundation namely the
到开源基金会，即
Eclipse Foundation is that we want to
Eclipse Foundation是我们想要的
solve that release issue I mean Java is
解决那个发行问题，我的意思是Java是
too slow to get updated so that was an
太慢而无法更新，因此
issue so we hope to solve that when he
问题，所以我们希望当他
for Jay will be there so it really
因为杰伊会在那里，所以真的
depends what you mean by the standard
取决于您所说的标准
but at the end of the day we would like
但最终，我们希望
to have something that is widely used so
拥有一些被广泛使用的东西
that's why we need to have some some
这就是为什么我们需要一些
common agreement on what is being used I
关于使用什么的共同协议
would reach to that agreement still have
将达成该协议仍然有
still has to be decided to be discussed
仍然需要决定要讨论
to me
对我来说
I say you know the eclipse foundation
我说你知道蚀的基础
patchy foundation and others I'm not
零散的基础和其他我不是
what you might call official standards
你可能称之为官方标准
bodies like w3c Oasis IETF and I don't
像w3c Oasis IETF这样的机构，我不
think they should be I think this is one
认为他们应该是我认为这是一个
of the problems that the JCP can have
JCP可能遇到的问题
got into and you know David's hinted at
走进去，你知道大卫的暗示
it you don't you shouldn't try and do
如果你不这样做，你不应该尝试去做
innovation within a standards
标准内的创新
organization a standards organization is
标准组织是
for standardizing things that have
用于标准化具有
innovated and have been deployed and
创新并已部署
people want to have portability or
人们想拥有便携性或
interoperability keep them separate so
互操作性使它们分开，因此
you know if Eve or J does really really
你知道夏娃还是J真的真的
well and the community including vendors
好，包括供应商在内的社区
believe there's some reason to
相信有某些理由
standardize all of it or parts of it
标准化全部或部分内容
then you know maybe we take it to a
那么你知道也许我们把它带到一个
waste as a right ear for spin up a
浪费作为旋转的右耳
completely new standards body but I
全新的标准机构，但我
honestly think that's a secondary thing
老实说这是次要的
you know these days with open source
你知道这些天开源
open standards tend to be good enough
开放标准往往足够好
for a lot of people an open standards
对很多人来说，开放标准
not something that goes through away so
不会消失的东西
they just it's something that's just
他们只是那只是
different yeah it's just just is so
是的，就是这样
widely yeah de-facto that's the yeah and
是的，事实上，是的，
that's one of the reasons when we you
这就是我们的原因之一
know when micro profile was founded it
知道微型档案的创建时间
was never really considered by the
从来没有真正考虑过
founders to be a standard per se because
创始人本身就是标准，因为
the idea was innovate and then submit
这个想法是创新的，然后提交
you know to the JCP right which we did
你知道我们做过的JCP权利
with config and now with it kind of
与配置，现在有了它
beginning to move into into Java Eve
开始涉足Java Eve
moving into the Eclipse Foundation one
进入Eclipse Foundation
question is what happens to the config
问题是配置发生了什么
jsr submission we're going to continue
jsr提交，我们将继续
down the path I just just to kind of
沿着这条路我只是想
complete the thought configuration from
从完成思想配置
a micro profile standpoint I mean our
微观观点我的意思是
goal from day one was to feed that back
从第一天开始的目标就是反馈
in to Java EE now with the introduction
现在通过介绍进入Java EE
of EE forge a kind of threw a wrench in
EE伪造一种把扳手
into those plans but we had already
那些计划，但我们已经
started down that path of producing a
开始了生产
configuration jsr for Java EE we're not
Java EE的配置jsr不是
going to discontinue that we've got the
我们将停止使用
spec leads all lined up the
规范导致所有排队
expert group is being formed we're going
我们正在组成专家组
to continue down that path because he 4j
继续走这条路，因为他4j
is still a work in progress so until
仍在进行中，因此直到
that is up and running and complete you
这样就可以运行并完善您
know we we want to continue the same
知道我们要继续一样
process and try to complete that jsr
处理并尝试完成该jsr
yeah there's no reason to stop you know
是的，没有理由阻止你知道
obviously we can't achieve making things
显然，我们无法实现创造事物
faster if we immediately stop there's
如果我们立即停在那里，速度更快
any kind of change that defeats the
改变失败的任何改变
point all right I think we are we out of
指出好吧，我认为我们是我们脱离了
time is it the 12:30 the yeah okay so I
现在是12:30是的，所以我
just wanted to be wary of you know the
只是想提防你知道
next session and everything assume there
下届会议，一切都假设在那里
is one right after this so thank you
在此之后是一个权利，所以谢谢
very much for coming thank all the
非常感谢大家的光临
attendees and the panelists if you'd
与会者和小组成员（如果您愿意）
like we can continue conversations
就像我们可以继续对话
outside in the hall all right thank you
在大厅外面好谢谢
very much
非常
[Applause]
[掌声]